Hey guys, what's up? The other day I came across advertising on Facebook for shapewear
and I thought I want to try this out because it's not simply shapewear as you may know it
but it is fashion and shapewear combined and I thought hey this looks really cool
let's try it out. Poppy Lush sent me some pieces to try and first is this combination with the
skirt and a bodysuit. Let's go! Now I may not be the typical shapewear wearer or shapewear
person body type but I really wanted to try this because I saw that the pieces go down to
extra small and the bra or rather the bodysuit I'm wearing is an extra small and the skirt is a small
I think the skirt would have fit an extra small as well it's a bit too white but it wasn't available
them extra small anyway the interesting thing is that it has built-in pennies
or rather pants already because they are like going down below the booty and it's
a built-in mesh shapewear part that is fused together with a skirt and we have
an open gusset so you can comfortably go to the bathroom without having to
undress all the tight stuff. Now I really like the bodysuit it has a slight push-up
effect and also in the body part here we have again the shapewear mesh inlay
which you can't see that good because of the skirt and it's on the inside but I
can show you some pictures of how this looks. I love about it that it really
does look like fashion so that's why I wanted to try this because I saw the
advertisement a few times and I wonder does it really work or is it really this
kind of innovative shape where that is really a merge of shape and fashion.
The next piece is a dress I wanted to try. That is not the dress. This should be the dress.
yeah so we have kind of a jeans optic and it's really heavy I don't know if you
can tell from the way it hangs but it's rather heavy because it's a lot of
fabric and it's also stretchy on the other hand but not in this direction so
much only in the length anyway let's try it I love this dress it's not a fetish
dress or something like that it's just a simple nice dress kind of yeah like a jeans look maybe
to check in the mirror and I love the cups they fit really good so I'm not wearing any underwear
I'm not wearing a bra and also we have the mesh shapewear underneath which is one piece
and here the open crotch area comes in really handy because you don't have to undress and it's
also recommended to not wear any on the way because then you would have a problem going to
the toilet again so it does not feel naked at all it's really comfortable also the cups they fit
really good and the yeah the shapewear mesh lining is everywhere here I love the stitching
the contrast stitching and I also think it makes a nice booty I thought that with the bodysuit and
the skirt as well it's not specifically advertised as the booty push-up but I think
it does work a bit like that too and yeah I just feel really tightly packed I struggled a bit to
get into it and get it over my hips so there's definitely a tight fit here even for me wearing a
small this is a small it was the smallest size underneath the zipper here there is a hook
hook line a line with hooks to hook the parts the sides together to have an even better
shape effect almost like a corset also it's really easy to close the zipper then
I have another dress and it's pink I mean I do know what I favor in my daily life this one
but I thought this was fun there is no hook line here but I can show you the
fabric inlay here I turn it inside out and here you can see the double mesh layer here
and the open gusset area which is surprisingly different color but it's also different material
so you can wash it better it's basically more hygienic this way that's how it looks
on the inside. It's pink. Let me check in the mirror.
I think it looks like
an office dress which you see in the movies when you have like a sexy secretary.
But I like the cut. It is the same fabric
than the first outfit.
So almost a bit shiny and
we have this kind of tiny dots printed on.
I actually wanted to have this in black because it's also available in black I think it would
be cooler in black but I'm wearing the smallest size and it was not available in black anymore
I think it's a nice fit and what I noticed there is something like a bra band sewn in from the
sides to the front that snatches everything together nicely and gives a bit more push-up
so we have no padding here but I think it still looks great also cleavage here
and it feels really tight and secure again and yeah it's kind of a funny feeling because
I'm basically wearing a bodysuit with a over skirt so to say I mean we have the
pants here again, the mesh pants.
But on the outside it looks like fashion.
Alright, let me close the zipper for a change.
I think it looks more sporty
in this way.
I prefer it with open zipper
and it does not feel like I'm wearing
only one piece. So no
under hair again and just this
ensemble
sewn together shapewear
fashion I think it's really cool and what I also noticed nothing was too short so far because I'm
with my 173 centimeters I'm quite tall I have a long upper body normally my problem is that
everything is just too short but not here which is great I like this and for the last piece I have
this jumpsuit here I'm going to change the last outfit is this basic catsuit and I love it just
because of the pockets here I love to have pockets where I can put my hands in and just chill
anyway um it's a pretty basic catsuit on the first glance but again we have padding here in a bra
so bra pads for a bit more shape and push and we have a double mesh layer here in this area
to snatch in the waist a bit more and there's also a seam just here below the butt cheeks to
push them a bit more so it's subtle but it's well thought through and I think this is a great way of
doing shapewear. Not the stuff that you have to put underneath your normal clothing, no ugly looking
underwear but it's a fashion and the finishing is really good the craftsmanship um I didn't see
any flaws so if you're curvy it's I think a great great shapewear to try out and look good and don't
have to worry about your overall outfit because you got all in one thanks to poppy lush for
sending these along. I had fun trying out this kind of shapewear I'm sure. I will
definitely wear this jumpsuit again because it's super comfy and also the
gray dress. Maybe I will get the pink dress in black. Just because then I would
wear it more often. Anyway I hope you enjoyed this video. Check out the
description text because I will put everything down there and leave a comment
tell me your favorite outfit if you have any experience with poppy lush already
I'd like to know and I will see you in the next video have a nice day bye